Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Miscellaneous (Box 21)
  - [65th birthday tribute to Richard Rodgers]: Envelope (oversize) (Box-folder 21/8)
Over and over again Jumbo
P.T. boat song NON-SHOW MUSIC
Paradox victory song/chant NON-SHOW MUSIC
Paris is really divine Peggy-Ann
Party that we're gonna have..., The Pipe Dream
Pas de deux Ghost Town
Pastoral The Valiant Years
Patrie, La The Valiant Years
Pears of Anjou, The Rex
Peggy! Peggy! Peggy-Ann
People will say we're in love Oklahoma!
Perfectly lovely couple Do I Hear a Waltz?
Perhaps Do I Hear a Waltz?
Peter's journey Babes in Arms
Philadelphia Do I Hear a Waltz?
Pierrot Love Me Tonight
Plant you now, dig you later Pal Joey
Please make me be good Let's Have Fun
Poor Apache, The Love Me Tonight
Poor Joe! Allegro
Poppa isn't Poppa anymore Two by Two
Poppa knows best Two by Two
Pore Jud is daid Oklahoma!
Possibly I'm cynical Allegro
Pottawatomie Too Many Girls
Prayer Too Many Girls
Prayer Hollywood Party
Prayer I Married an Angel
Prince is giving a ball Cinderella
Princesse Zenobia ballet, La On Your Toes
Priscilla Say Mama
Prism, plums and prunes Up Stage and Down
Processional The Sound of Music
Progress One Dam Thing After Another
Put him away! Two by Two
Puzzlement, A The King and I
Quand notre vieux monde etait tout neuf Ever Green
Queen Elizabeth The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Rachel State Fair
Real nice clambake, A Carousel
Reincarnation Hollywood Party
Requiescat in pace The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Return from Dunkirk The Valiant Years
Rex Rex
Rhythm Babes in Arms
Rhythm The Show Is On
Rock NON-SHOW MUSIC
Rose of summer Ghost Town
Royal Bangkok Academy, The The King and I
San Marco Do I Hear a Waltz?
Saturday night Two by Two
Sea killer The Valiant Years
Send for me Simple Simon
Sentimental me! The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Shakespeare One Dam Thing After Another
Shakespeare of 1922 NON-SHOW MUSIC
Shall we dance? The King and I
She could shake the maracas Too Many Girls
Shortest day of the year, The The Boys from Syracuse
Shorty, the gunner NON-SHOW MUSIC
Show him the way Say Mama
Shuffle Betsy
Silver threads Bad Habits of 1925
Simpatica They Met in Argentina
Since I remember you Winkle Town
Sing Betsy
Sing for your supper The Boys from Syracuse
Sitting on the porch in the moonlight Allegro
Sixteen going on seventeen The Sound of Music
Ski troops The Valiant Years
Slaughter on Tenth Avenue On Your Toes
Sleep, weary head MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Sleeping beauty Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
Sleepyhead The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
So far Allegro
So long, farewell The Sound of Music
So much you loved me Rex
Softer than a kitten Simple Simon
Softer than a kitten Follow Thru
Soliloquy Carousel
Some enchanted evening South Pacific
Someone like you Do I Hear a Waltz?
Someone should tell them One Dam Thing After Another
Someone should tell them A Connecticut Yankee
Someone woke up Do I Hear a Waltz?
Something doesn't happen Two by Two
Something good The Sound of Music
Something, somewhere Two by Two
Something wonderful The King and I
Son-of-a-gun is nothing but a tailor!, The Love Me Tonight
Song of Russia The Prisoner of Zenda
Song of the roustabouts, The Jumbo
Song of the high seas Victory at Sea
Song of the king The King and I
Sound of music, The The Sound of Music
Speeches are gold The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Spic and Spanish Too Many Girls
Spring is here Spring Is Here
Spring is here I Married an Angel
State Fair State Fair
Stay Do I Hear a Waltz?
Stay home with a book Too Many Girls
Steady as you go NON-SHOW MUSIC
Straight down the middle Lawrence of Arabia
Straight down the middle I Picked a Daisy
Strangers Androcles and the Lion
Strength is my weakness Androcles and the Lion
Strength is my weakness Two by Two
Submarines in a calm sea Victory at Sea
Such good fun I Remember Mama
Sunday Flower Drum Song
Sunny Pacific Islands, The Victory at Sea
Surrey with the fringe on top, The Oklahoma!
Suzy development Pipe Dream
Suzy is a good thing Pipe Dream
Sweet sixty-five I'd Rather Be Right
Sweet Thursday Pipe Dream
Sweetenheart Simple Simon
Sweetest sounds, The No Strings
Sweethearts of the team, The Too Many Girls
Take and take and take I'd Rather Be Right
Take him Pal Joey
Take the moment Do I Hear a Waltz?
Tartar song, The MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Te Deum Rex
Tell it to the Marines MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Tell me Rex
Tell me I know how to love I Married an Angel
Temple dance By Jupiter
Temple of Minerva, The By Jupiter
Tempt me not! Too Many Girls
Ten cents a dance Simple Simon
Ten minutes ago Cinderella
Tennis champs The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
Terrible mother Lawrence of Arabia
Thank you so much Do I Hear a Waltz?
That terrific rainbow Pal Joey
That's for me! State Fair
That's the rhythm of the day MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 7]
That's the song of Paree Love Me Tonight
That's the way it happens Me and Juliet
The boy I left behind me By Jupiter
The merrie merrie Bad Habits of 1925
There are kings Rex
There is nothin' like a dame South Pacific
There's a boy in Harlem Fools for Scandal
There's a small hotel MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 9]
There's music in you Main Street to Broadway
There's nothin' so bad for a woman Carousel
There's so much more America's Sweetheart
Thinkin' Pipe Dream
Thinking Do I Hear a Waltz?
This can't be love The Boys from Syracuse
This funny world Betsy
This goes up MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
This is my night to howl A Connecticut Yankee
This is not Long Island Spring Is Here
This isn't heaven State Fair
This nearly was mine South Pacific
This rescue is a terrible calamity! MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
Thou swell A Connecticut Yankee
Three B's, The On Your Toes
Three musketeers, The The Garrick Gaieties (1925)
Tick-tick Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
Tide pool, The Pipe Dream
Tiki-pu NON-SHOW MUSIC
Time I Remember Mama
Tiny flat near Soho Square, A Lido Lady
To have and to hold Allegro
To please my king Rex
Too good for the average man MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 10]
Too many girls Too Many Girls
Town hall tonight! The Girl Friend
Tramping along Peggy-Ann
Tramping along Peggy-Anne
Treaty, my sweetie, with you, A I'd Rather Be Right
Tree in the park, A Peggy-Ann
Try NON-SHOW MUSIC
Try again tomorrow MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
Turkey in the straw The Girl Friend
Twin soliloquies South Pacific
Twinkle in your eye, A I Married an Angel
Two by two Do I Hear a Waltz?
Two little people Carousel
Two more [loves] Allegro
Two of a kind The Girl Friend
Two short years Allegro
Two to eleven Lido Lady
Two-a-day for Keith On Your Toes
Uncle Chris! I Remember Mama
Velvet paws Androcles and the Lion
Very special day, A Me and Juliet
Virtue wins the day You'll Never Know
Wait till you see her By Jupiter
Wait till you see her Oklahoma!
Waiting The King and I
Waiting for the leaves to fall Ever Green
Wake up little theatre Me and Juliet
Waltz for a ball Cinderella
We kiss in a shadow The King and I
We want you to feel at home NON-SHOW MUSIC
We will be together State Fair
We're going to balance the budget I'd Rather Be Right
We're gonna be all right Do I Hear a Waltz?
We're on our way NON-SHOW MUSIC
We're staying here I Remember Mama
Wee golden warrior, The Rex
Wee little China rose The Chinese Lantern
Western people funny The King and I
What a lovely day for a wedding Allegro
What can you do with a man? The Boys from Syracuse
What did I have that I don't have I Picked a Daisy
What did I have that I don't have Lawrence of Arabia
What do we do? We fly! Do I Hear a Waltz?
What do you want with money? Hallelujah, I'm a Bum
What kind of man I Remember Mama
What's the use of talking The Garrick Gaieties (1926)
What's the use of wond'rin' Carousel
When I go on the stage One Dam Thing After Another
When I go out walkin' with my baby Oklahoma!
When it dries Two by Two
When men are in love The Prisoner of Zenda
When the children are asleep Carousel
When the old world was new Ever Green
When you're falling in love with... I Married an Angel
When? I Remember Mama
Where is my son Rex
Where or when Babes in Arms
Where we came from I Remember Mama
Who are you? The Boys from Syracuse
Why do I? The Girl Friend
Why have you eyes I Married an Angel
Why me? Two by Two
Why? Rex
Why? why? why? The King and I
Wildcats are on a rampage, The Allegro
Will you marry me? Allegro
Willing and eager State Fair
Willow pattern NON-SHOW MUSIC
Winston depressed The Valiant Years
Winston is back in office The Valiant Years
Winston is back The Valiant Years
Wiowani, Josi-Mosi, and Mee Mee themes NON-SHOW MUSIC
Wish them well Allegro
Without love The Prisoner of Zenda
Without my money Two by Two
Woman needs something like that, A Love Me Tonight
Women Jumbo
Women are women I Married an Angel
Women without men I Remember Mama
Wonderful guy, A South Pacific
Worst of friends, The The Prisoner of Zenda
Would I not love you Rex
Writer writes at night, A I Remember Mama
Yankee, go home! No Strings
Yatata, yatata, yatata Allegro
Yodel if you can I Married an Angel
You Two by Two
You always love the same girl A Connecticut Yankee
You are beautiful Flower Drum Song
You are never away Allegro
You are so lovely and I'm so lonely MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 5]
You are so fair Babes in Arms
You are what I need A Connecticut Yankee
You could not please me more I Remember Mama
You couldn't please me more Two by Two
You don't tell me No Strings
You have cast your shadow on the sea The Boys from Syracuse
You have got to have a rudder on the ark Two by Two
You musn't kick it around Pal Joey
You never had it so good Allegro
You took advantage of me MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 2]
You walked in State Fair
You'll never walk alone Carousel
You're nearer Too Many Girls
You're on the Lido now MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES-- [M.S. 3]
You're too wonderful for me! Winkle Town
You've got the best of me They Met in Argentina
You've got to be carefully taught South Pacific
Younger than springtime South Pacific
Zip! Pal Joey
Zoo Hallelujah, I'm a Bum